ME
The best snacks in HISAKA!
The second half of the project to decide the number one snack that members and their friends would like to have in their dressing rooms.
Tonight, we've taken the liberty of categorizing the snacks in the "Slightly Sour Taste" section, and we've got this one, and this one, and this one.
Kubo said this is the fried chicken flavor... and it was taken in July... and I've been eating them since I was a kid.
I've been eating them since I was a kid.
I eat it like it's air.
Who's that?
Yamashita.
Yamashita. Did you serve a lot?
Yes, a lot.
It's good, isn't it?
It's a classic.
I'm not the one with the dimples, but...
I'm gonna do this one with my mouth wide open, and then I'm gonna do this one with my teeth, right?
Yeah, that's good.
That's great.
Oh, that's good.
Oh, this is good.
It's good.
Who's never had this before?
I've never had it before.
I didn't know... that Kinoko served it to me... and I've never even seen it before... in a convenience store like Eriko.
I don't go here.
They're good for you... and you've never spent a penny.
Yamashita... you've got a very broad palette.
I'm a snack queen. I love sweets.
I love sweets... scones are now packaged like this... I'd already rank this as my No. 1 super standard sub... if it were a snack. If it were a snack, I'd be using the devil's tongue.
Who recommends this?
It's good.
It's good, isn't it?
It's delicious. I would eat the whole bag if I ate it at home while watching TV.
That's cute.
That's a cute episode.
I usually eat the whole bag.
I don't need to watch TV, so I just eat it because there's nothing to eat.
I don't want to eat it all in one sitting.
It's great as a popcorn batter, and then you can have it with pâté.
I've been a munchie ever since it came out, and it was on my grade-school graduation letter, and it was my favorite food, and I was like...
I still love this guy from the sky.
Who's this?
I was at a friend's house and her grandmother made this recipe for me.
My grandma's stomach was on fire.
My grandma ate it and said, "I'm burning up!
Grandma's Caramutelle!
Yum, yum, yum, yum!
Yum, yum, yum!
Fried onion glue nest.
Yum! Yum!
I love it!
So, what do you do with this, this recipe, this judgment call, this is a wonderful glue nest, it's delicious, I love it, I love it.
What about this one? I'll take that as a yes.
Yes.
Yes, sir.
I thought you said yes.
Then I'll say yes.
Yes!
It's a sister product of Karamucho.
Suppamucho!
Oh, it's delicious... but I don't have it on hand... or sour munchies.
I don't really touch it...
No, I don't like sour munchies either.
I don't serve sour food.
Plum-flavored challenge
Oh, so it's plum.
Plum.
Yay!
No, it's not.
It's not what you think it is.
No?
Why not?
I thought you were messing with me. Yes. Do you like sweets?
I love the smell when you open it... it's not so good.
I'm not a big fan of sour food, but this is really good. I'm not sure if it's a dream or a dream. It's good.
What's that? I thought it would be more sour.
The little red ones have a richer flavor and are tastier.
The color.
They have a lot of powder on them.
It's nice to find something like that in a snack.
What's this?
Shiitake mushrooms.
What are these?
Is this candy too? Someone must have brought hoshi shiitake mushrooms.
I'd like it if they gave it to me in a little bag like that.
It's just as it is in the scene... "It's rustic..." I'm wondering if that's what he meant.
I'm just saying it's naive, but... he says he's going on a horse... and then he says he's going on a motorcycle.
And then he said, "I'm going on a horse," and then he said, "I'm going on a motorcycle.
It's good, it's good, it's good, but it tastes like...
But the taste is... it's really addictive and you eat a lot of them.When you get addicted to something, it becomes really addictive and you eat a lot of them!
Wow, it's addictive!
Delicious!
How did you come across this?
My mom gave it to me.
It's so delicious, I'm addicted to it!
What's this?
Oh, flapper!
Zurno Veggie Tabs
Do you know how many different kinds of acai there are?
I don't know!
I don't know what this is, but there's some kind of developer feedback on the side of it.
"Developer's Comments"?
Yeah, that's what I wrote.
It's like, "That's what I like to see in a human being.
That's what I'm talking about.
It's delicious.
It's good.
My grandpa eats it every day.
He's healthy.
Yes, Grandpa eats it every day, just like that.
Grandpa eats it every day, just like that.
I'm eating, I'm eating and then
You're drinking.
I'm eating.
With tea.
But you know what? This is good.
It's good.
Delicious.
Next.
Well, I put them in this time.
Hot chips.
Mr. Hisada?
Yes.
They were part of the story.
Tsutsuri bought them for me the other day.
That's right.
I think we all had them the other day.
It's delicious.
This is...
This is really good!
It looks great with the uniform.
Yum!
What's up with that?
It's amazing, isn't it?
Seriously.
I seriously don't know what's cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute, cute.
It's soooo silly!
Wow, it tastes expensive!
Wow.
This is seriously weak.
There it is, the trifle!
No. 1 in the world of trifles.
Gourmet Mono-Smith
Here we go.
I don't even know some of these guys around here.
I don't know!
This is me. Actually, I learned it from Umezawa.
And I'm hooked!
Once I try it, I'll go out and buy more.
I bet you two would love it!
I'm sure you two would love it! Yum!
It's so good! Yum!
If you eat it, it's a truffle!
That's right!
This is for adults now.
Yum!
It's a bit of a classy side dish.
This is the kind of thing you eat with a glass of wine or something.
Too good!
They also have sea urchin.
Sea urchin?
That's not good either!
Where do you find these?
At Seijo Ishii.
Oh, Seijo Ishii?
Now that's a cool way to put it!
Oh, cool! Seijo Ishii ni umaisaisaisaisai, now that's a cool way to say it!
That's good!
You're just like a big sister!
And the snacks you're eating.
Here!
Look at this souvenir!
It doesn't look like Hokkaido.
It's like that!
Like jaggery pokkles.Like a jagapokkle.
It's like a jagapokkur, right?
It's like a jagapokkur, like a jagabokkur, like a jagabokkur, like a jagabokkur.
I'm a souvenir type... but really, it's just as good as Jagga Hookl...
It's just as good as Jaguar Hookl.
This is delicious!
This is so good!
It's got that sweet onion taste afterwards.
Onions!
This is so good.
That's me.
I've been wondering about this.
What's this?
I like this kind of squid... sold at 7-Eleven.
It's spicy too, but you can eat it as it is, but I like to break it up into bite-size pieces.
This is in the snack section, so I guess it's a snack, but I eat it as a snack.
Wow!
It's so good!
Yum!
I'm not a big fan of the salty kind, but I do like this kind.
I'm not much of a snack guy, but I love this stuff!
I'm having a beer today, but I like beer! Beer good! Beer good!
Beer good!
And now, by unanimous vote.
The winner of the other salty flavor is...
Potato Cottons!
Congratulations!
Potecotan is going to sell!
Potecotan is coming!
Potecotan will sell like hotcakes!
I wouldn't mind if it was a different tournament.
The members are strong.
It's a good year.
Maybe I'm right. Maybe I'm right.
I've been wearing that for a while now.
I like it.
But this time we used snacks.
Or rice crackers.
Candy canes.
I'd also like some ice cream.
Bread is bread
Don!
It's time for Nogizaka Kenshoku Chugakusei Shikara Bananama, thank you very much.
Nogizaka-chan!
And now... Nogizaka-chan!
Oh, who are you?
Who are you?
And it's been a while since we've been over there... but what do you mean?
This girl.
The winning quiz team will get one of you for sure!
Each one of you will get one of these!
What?
That's 4000 yen!
4000 yen a piece!
You know Ume?
I've been wondering about this place.
I know everything.
That's why I've been wanting to try it.
Really?
If it was plum, I could have eaten it in three bites.
She's not a giant.
By the way, Mr. Himura doesn't know the answer this time either.
If I buy it, can I eat it?
If there is, I'll give the quiz to Tamura on behalf of all the teams.
You can ask for up to 3 hints per question, and the person who answers correctly with fewer hints will get 5 points.
But you can only answer once. The team with the most points wins.
How confident are you that the 4th graders will be able to answer the questions, since we've been together for so long, and we're not sure if we'll be able to get along with them, or if we'll be able to pay them.
I'll try it this way.
I think I'll give it a try.
Are you talking to Iyamoto Renka?
Mr. Enka asked if he could take my picture and I talked to him the other day.
Yamamoto is a rather that, I've talked to him and I've talked to him and I've talked to him and I've talked to him and I've talked to him and I've talked to him one on one in his personal program.
I'm the captain of Yumehana and I'm sure you have the data of Maana.
I'm sure you've got some data on Maana, from afar.
If you win, I'll give you one of those.
Really?
I've prepared two of them.
Got it!
Good luck.
Leave it to me.
Ice Village Tamura
Ice Village!
Horny.
Horny, ice village, horny.
horny horny
Yada
horny hornyhorny horny
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
Have you ever seen a girl like this?
Question 1
First information
Her bag is as small as an Airpotts.
That's it.
That's all I have.
Please answer the question.
I don't know.
Airpots are like this, right?
They're pretty small, aren't they?
If you've seen this one, you'll know what I'm talking about.
Well then...
What do you want to do with this?
Do we go through with this or do we answer?
We're in agreement.
Well, if he says he'll go, then...
So, do you want to hold off on that, or do you want to go with the plan, or...
I'll ask you one more question.
What are you going to do?
As soon as you get the right answer...
I can't answer the other one.
I see.
I don't get it, Mr. Himura.
I don't know.
Shall we go?
I'm going.
Yeah.
Strong. Here.
If they answer correctly, this problem is over.
Kubo, will Iwamoto's team answer here, too?
We've narrowed it down to two now.
I don't know.
I don't know. I'll just have to wait a little longer for the Ume team to get it right.
I'll just have to wait and see if the Ume team takes me off.
I'm not sure if it's too much or too little, but how about this?
Aaahhhh!
I'll have to go to the second clue, so here's the second clue I recently ate sashimi for the first time and I've never eaten sashimi before
I can't answer this question.
I want to go... but I don't know if this is the right place...
I'm sure it's regulated!
You were a catcher at the time... but you only killed the fish...
Open, please. Saya Hanakawa!
Ms. Kimura, you're up.
I like the one that's good. Many of them brought their own makeup tools, but I didn't get the impression that they had a lot of luggage, since they were using the makeup artist's tools.
Luggage? Sashimi? In Hokkaido?
I had a hard time deciding on the sashimi, but at first I had to choose between my bag and Yuna Shibata's. I went to sushi with Yuna. I promised Yuna that we would go to sushi.
So you can eat fish?
I've definitely eaten fish before. I said, "So," and she said, "Hanakawa." I was surprised that she hadn't eaten in Hokkaido.
I'm sure some of our acquaintances are writers in Hokkaido and they don't eat seafood.
I don't know, Mr. Himura, you know, Inoue is a beautiful woman, so to put it another way, I don't need all this baggage, you know?
I got the impression that she's a natural on the stomach, and she's the best in the group. You've never had sashimi? I think she's going to say something shocking like, "You've never eaten sashimi?
So, which of the two is the correct member?
Then, is there a correct answer for either of these two... ahhhhh! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH!!!! Ohhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh I love it!
If you answer ok to all teams with 3 clues, you get 1 point for each tag.
The last one is the most vocal one in Nogizaka46
I've heard it from everyone's ears and it's a phenomenon that no one has ever heard of before.
I'm buying from Litco, so maybe you're someone who doesn't have a loud image.
I'm sure you'll be able to find the answer to your question in the last clue.
Zubaba Shibata work
I have the loudest voice.
Stingy or tiny?
I was thinking of Hisana's idea that it's because I'm tiny.
I don't think she'd say "tsutsuki".
I think she'll say "figure".
I don't think she'll say "appearance".
I don't think she's going to show it, but I think she's going to show it.
But she seems to have a medium sized bag.
Yeah, I don't know about that.
I don't know about sashimi either.
Okay, Umeyama...
Shokichi Shokichi seems to have a loud voice.
Oh, he sounds like he's going to say something a little different, like he's never eaten sashimi before.
That sounds like something he would say
But there's squid...
No, sashimi!
That sounds like something you'd eat.
I'm sure it's possible.
Iwakubo.
Same as Iwakubo.
Shinobu Shoyoshi
But Kawachicha is the same.
I haven't seen her with that much makeup stuff.
Seriously.
I wonder if any of them are right.
Who has the correct answer, Tamura?
The correct answer is Yuna Shibata.
Wow!Wow.
Yuna, you definitely have a knack for this.
me
ahhhhh!
ahhhhh...
I had two choices for sushi, so I had two choices with Yang, Yuna.
Wait a minute, I promised sushi.
She said she likes sushi.
I like sushi.
Not recently.
Not recently?
Last year, I guess.
I hadn't eaten raw sashimi until then.
I've never had raw fish.
When I go to sushi restaurants, I eat salmon roe and eggs.
You know, frog patterns, that kind of thing.
But sashimi, well, well, well, well, well, you know, these exchanges ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah ah. AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH
I have a bag, just in case it would be noticeable if I didn't have it when I get on the train, but really, it's just a pochette.
I don't carry makeup and such, but I can usually get by with a pocket full of earphones, my cell phone, moisturizing lipstick, and that kind of thing.
I'm not sure how many years ago a survey showed that I could be number one in Nogizaka if I kept my voice loud enough.
Yashi-I don't know if it's people who say they're confident about their voices or if it's people who do the "kakki" thing...
Kakki, say "yoo-hoo" a little.
If you start too soon, you might get crushed.
Please give me the loudest yakkety-yakkety-yakk.
Yoo-hoo!
It's huge.
Bigger than anything I've heard in the past.
Hoshino was so tiny.
Yoo-hoo!
Yoo-hoo-hoo
Yoo-hoo
Un-un was big
Then let's go to Masayoshi and do some aori
Yoo-hoo, please
Yoo-hoo
It's big!
Yoo-hoo, yoo-hoo, yoo-hoo!
Yoo-hoo!
I'll read it to you or something.
Okay, I'll just...
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh
Biggest yoo-hoo
Here you go.
Yoo-hoo!
Low.
That's low.
Low... low... low...
Come on, Shibata, let's go.
We've got to be the biggest.
I've got to keep my voice up.
Come on, Shibata.
Please do.
Yoo-hoo!
Laughing.
Not so much.
LOL ahhhhh! AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH AHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHHH ahhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh I'll have one please please please please please please please please please please yippeeee! oh wow!
huge!
Huge.
I wish I could get this much out of you.
I used to be able to.
That's not true.
I used to be a worse drinker.
It was the dirtiest.
Yee-haw was the dirtiest.
So, one point for Mr. Kokohimo.
No way... no way... no way...
No way...
That's amazing!
Any girls here?
Question 2: The first piece of information...
I know a lot about whales.
By the way...
She was interested in whales, did some research on them, and fell in love with them.
This is hard.
If you remember talking about whales, even a little bit...
So that's all for this week.
I'm sure you'll all have to wait until next week to find out!
I'm Asahi Kanagawa, this is Yuna Shibata.
I'm going to say "A" now, so please guess what "A" is.
Yes, I'm Yuna Shibata.
What?
Huh?
Uh, the pain of going home.
I dyed my hair a different color.
I don't know, I don't know.
Okay, well, please subscribe to our channel.Okay, well, please subscribe to our channel.